Contact

12, Olowolagba Street, Iwaya, Lagos, Nigeria. +2347035507270 (Mobile) victoryikuomola@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/victory-ikuomola (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Git

Critical Thinking
Programming Languages

Victory Ikuomola

Software Engineer {PHP, NodeJs, Python}

Lagos State, Nigeria

Summary

An experienced, and efficient software engineer.

With a primary focus on back-end web development, I develop and maintain highly-optimized and scaleable web applications, web services, and application programming interfaces that meet their objectives.

I am a graduate of Computer Science and information technology, from Bowen University, with verifiable years of experience in this domain.

Skill set: PHP, Laravel, Yii2, Slim, Javascript, Node JS, Python, Flask, Django, Dart, SQL, Git.

Experience

Trustvas limited
1 year 5 months

Mid level software engineer March 2023 - Present (7 months) Lagos State, Nigeria

Software Development Intern May 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Lagos, Nigeria

Responsible for the Maintenance of the client portal.

Building a subscription endpoint.

Involved in the Integration of billing and subscription service with MTN madapi. Integration of push bank transfer service with A new short code for Zenith bank.

Bincom ICT Solutions
Junior Associate Software Engineer
December 2022 - August 2023 (9 months)

Lagos State, Nigeria

Team lead(PHP Backend team): Responsible for leading, assisting and coordinating the Backend team.

Built and maintained digital web solutions on Laravel framework and YII2 framework.

Bincom ICT Solutions Software Development Intern August 2020 - May 2021 (10 months) Yaba, Lagos

Maintenance of the Social lender API

Development of web and mobile-based applications

Bincom Dev Center
Data Science facilitator
November 2020 - February 2021 (4 months)
Lagos, Nigeria

Education

bowen university iwo
Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Sience And Information
Technology · (2015 - November 2021)